蟹堡王
翻译  1440kHz
该数数我的钱了
Time to count me money
我的钱
My money
章鱼哥
Squidward
你钱不在我这
I don't have your money
我知道是谁拿了你的钱
I know who took your money
快说  我会让你亲眼看见
Tell me and I'll let you watch
他被我碎尸万段
as I tear him into a thousand little pieces
又被我拼回去
mesh 'em back together
然后又被我碎尸万段一遍
and tear him into a thousand little pieces
all over again
是我干的  蟹老板
It was me, Mr. Krabs
求你别把我碎尸万段
Please don't tear me into a thousand little pieces
又拼回去  然后再碎尸万段一遍啊
and mesh me back together and tear me to pieces again
你干嘛要拿  海绵宝宝
Why, SpongeBob?
是要给钱清理打磨一下
To clean and polish it
好家伙
Well, I'll be a sea monkey's uncle
下一批钱来了  海绵宝宝
Here's another batch, SpongeBob
包在我身上  蟹老板
I'm on it, Mr. K
我的钱从来没这么好看过
Me money never looked better
谢了  海绵宝宝
Thanks, SpongeBob